rsaevents.com 2011-01-06

# Privacy | Spykercars

**Privacy statement**  
This web site is administered by Spyker Cars N.V. (Spyker).

When you visit this web site Spyker may collect personal data about you, either directly (where you are asked to provide the data) or indirectly. Spyker will, however, only use these personal data in accordance with the purposes set forth in this privacy statement and is committed to safeguarding the personal information collected. This privacy statement sets out the purposes of Spyker's data processing in respect of this web site, the use of cookies and how to effect your rights in respect of your personal data.

**Purposes of processing**  
Spyker collects and processes information about customers and visitors to its web site to conduct its business, to inform and make available and deliver products and services that may be of interest to you and for the development of web statistics. The information you provide will be used to offer services that you may find helpful (provided you have not opted out to receive such services) and to deliver products and/or services ordered via the web shop of Spyker and to contact you when necessary, e.g. to notify you about functionality changes to the web site. The information you provide may also be made available to third parties for delivery purposes.

**Sensitive data**  
Spyker does not seek to collect sensitive personal data (such as data revealing political opinions, religious beliefs or data concerning health or sex life) through this site. If Spyker does seek to collect such data, your prior consent hereto will be asked. Please note that, by providing Spyker with unsolicited sensitive personal data you consent to our using those data as described above. 

**Cookies**  
Spyker may gather and analyse information regarding usage of this web site, including domain name, the number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited and length of user session. This information may be gathered by using a cookie. A cookie is a small text file placed on your hard drive by our web page server. You can choose whether or not to use a cookie by altering the settings of your browser. A cookie will make the use of this web site faster and easier.

**Third party sites**  
Please note that this privacy statement does not extend to third party sites linked to this web site. 

**How to contact Spyker**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or our data processing activities, you can contact us via: info@spykercars.com.

**Amendments**  
Spyker reserves the right to modify sections of this privacy statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.
